Guide to the Herbert J. Gezork Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Personal Mementos, Series VIII
  - Inauguration as President of Andover Newton
    - Invitations, 1951 (Box 16)
    - Program, 1951 (Box 16)
    - Clippings, 1951 (Box 16)
    - Telegrams, Letters of regret, Letters of congratulations, Letters of acceptance, 1951 (Box 16)
  - Documentation of life and work
    - Clippings, articles, service programs, letters relating to Gezork's academic career, 1931-1981, no date (Box 17)
      A list of items in this box is available in the first folder.
    - Clippings, articles, service programs, letters relating to Gezork's academic career, 1943-1972, no date (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous biographical documentation (Box 20)
      Material relating to amnesty petition, retirement as President of ANTS, biographical material, photographs, pamphlet on Gezork's Lowell Lectures, obituary; other miscellaneous material
    - Personal memo pads, address books, diaries, 1937–1965 (Box 21)
    - Notepads logging lectures and sermons with date delivered and location, 1943–1977 (Box 22)
    - Notebooks in German (Box 22)
    - Diplomas; brass plaque in appreciation of 10 years as ANTS President and 1 year president of American Baptist Convention (Box 22)
  - Slides
    - Personal and travel slides, including from Canada, Europe, and Latin America (Box 18)